I just want more of it.
So shiny, so beautiful.
People's thoughts and feelings, their desires, everything.
Oh God, I want to collect all their different colors and blur the lines between them.
Only if we spend the night.
That was the condition I gave to him for our next date.
Of course, only with this one.
I'm not going to do that with the miner.
I'll have a wholesome date with him next week.
There's no real reason for the order.
This is how it usually is with me.
I always try to cross the line with everything.
If you needed to know if I was suited for this sort of thing,
I would say probably not.
Do you even realize what you've done?
You stayed at his house, didn't you?
Well, you see, I didn't have a reason to say no.
There's something wrong with you!
Is he angry that I spent the night at some guy's house?
Hey, why do you look so sad and miserable all of a sudden?
Does this mean that I crossed a line that I can't possibly take back?
I don't know how it feels, really.
Trying to make someone special cross their ever-present line?
Or the pleasant feeling of having your own line eroded?
Joy and anger, sadness, all these emotions.
I'm sure I was never meant to feel them.
Because...
I feel so disconnected from everything.
Why do you keep doing this?
You see, you're not suited for it.
And why not?
We've almost arrived.
Oh.
You were fast asleep there.
Are you really tired?
What?
Not really.
That's because I was up with a young guy all last night.
So we're going to spend the night in Otomi?
Huh?
It's like we're having an affair.
What's that?
I'm not married, so this would be pre-honeymoon.
Wait, I'm not even sure if that's right either.
Well, actually, I mean...
It was just a joke.
It's true.
You
So how have things been lately with you, Hanabi?
Why do you ask?
Well, it just seems you're not seen with Mugi at all lately.
I came because you said you wanted my advice on something, so why talk about me?
We thought we could learn a lot from your relationship experience.
You were always considered such an attractive couple. You guys had everyone's attention.
What? Seriously?
As you see, we're curious about what happened.
Definitely. So, tell us.
I haven't seen him since the summer.
What? Why?
But it's the end of October.
Uh, well, it's just that it's better we don't see each other now.
You're so mature for your age, Hanabi.
Here you go, miss.
Thank you.
It's nice being around you. You're surprisingly easy to get along with.
Huh? You think so?
I just stopped putting on an axe since it didn't really matter anymore.
I think you should act more like this at school.
Absolutely not.
Hey, don't drop your ice cream.
Huh?
Hmm.
Hmm?
What?
Really?
Tell me.
Why do you do this?
How the hell should I know?
Probably because it's my life's work.
Wow.
This view is just incredible.
Seriously, I could care less about the dumb view.
It sure is windy today.
I don't want to have to beat around the bush here, but I need to know what this relationship
is huh I'm so tired right now huh are you okay
do you need some water honestly I I'm sorry I'll up I know what why don't we
rest first hmm what I'll go get you some water what that really Wow I need to
think from a different angle why did things end up like that back then what's
missing oh are you really not going to drink anything seriously no I can't
possibly this feels so good I remember going to a hot spring with my mother
once it was nice I bet the stars are incredible too bad I can't see them
without my glasses I feel so lucky it's like a dream I'm on a trip with miss
Minagawa all right let's watch the stars no seriously bad I'm such a fool I always
do this when it counts this is awful I wanted us to see the stars here back you
took a long time there huh what happened to your glasses because I'm serious about
this please don't laugh when I tell you this the stars the flowers all the
beautiful things in the world exist only to be compared to you so um is the room
too dark for you I'm okay with it helps me to see the moon I'm sorry it seems I can
see even less in the dark um what's wrong what's the problem what did you mean when
you said I didn't need to stop what are you referring to how do you not remember come on
now me being a slut and all oh it's because you like it right so you don't have to stop
huh you make it sound like it's just some innocent hobby do I not have it right
you're right I do it because I like it but I'm asking you how how does it make you feel
hmm really are you serious you have to think on it what is there to think about wait what am I
feeling what is this why am I nervous I don't I don't I don't like it so you have to hate it
hmm what am I even saying right now will you hate me if I don't get upset I will god I sound
pathetic this isn't me he's throwing me off my whole game I see but I I love you
I will still love you hypothetically could you really love someone even if they continue to hate
you I would gather most people would say no even if you say you really love someone part of your
feelings are connected to the notion that this person also loves you in the same way normally
trying to actually love someone unconditionally it's unthinkable I don't get it why that's not even
normal how could you possibly feel that way about me why is that
it's sort of difficult to explain exactly why I love you but you're a literature teacher
it's just that I want the person I love to live a happy life that they'll enjoy
that actually sounds so heartfelt because it is then that won't do
it's not enough how's that enough for you why can't you want more
once I start wanting more I don't think I'll be able to quit
I won't be able to stop my desires I'm scared that I might just
I might hurt the person I care about someday
I think you're wrong about that I believe if you want them so badly
even if they hurt you in the end if they're special to you and the pain is done with care
they'll be able to become stronger
wow I didn't know it could feel this good
I can't believe I'm actually saying this but I finally feel connected
oh my head's killing me so is mine did I really drink that much last night
do you even remember what happened between us last night huh
of course I remember that
Mina I mean Akane
my first name that's something new
is that okay
I'm fine with it
will will you please marry me
people can't always change that easily
I for one still calculate my moves
and this new feeling might just be an illusion
so what do I do
okay
I'll cheat on you all the time
really
you're sure
you're okay with all the cheating
I'm going to have to check and see
is this really an illusion
can people really change
some people will say no
but I'm sure what they truly feel is
you've been here long
no
wow
so um
this feels like a first date
they think
if they can't change them
there was that time
we went over to the
then they don't want to see anyone else change them
either
was that considered a date
that's what I think it is
that's so
I'm just kidding
let's go
okay
I realize that our first date
is probably our last
do you like tall places
yes
it's so exciting
looking down at the ground
from way up here
reminds me that people long ago
didn't get to do things like this
I remember
there was a time
when I thought I glimpsed
Akane's true feelings
when she was less guarded
believe it or not
it seems that I really enjoy
teaching people
is that true?
you never find it tedious at all?
huh?
no
not in the least
I wouldn't take this job
if I found it unpleasant
one day
when I die
I have no desire
to be remembered
by anyone
isn't that
the opposite
from what you're doing?
I mean
isn't teaching
all about being
an influence on someone?
but it seems
when I'm a teacher
I get to stay a teacher
in all their memories
nothing more than that
I thought I understood her
in that precise moment
it's that
she doesn't feel comfortable
unless she's attached
to something
be it teacher
woman
or someone older
I came to realize
the reason she clings to roles
is simple
it's because she actually
wants to be freed
from all her boredom
if that's it
well then
one day soon
I'll free you
thank you
back there
on the observation deck
I like it for the same reason
as you
it's all exciting
with all of the cool new things
we're able to do now
it makes me want to go
and try them all
I like that we have more options
you know
it's like it gives us
that much more freedom
I get that
huh
so
so now
I promise
I have news
I'm getting married
huh
it's something new
that I haven't been able
to try out yet
I think I want to
give it a go
it seems people can change
but it's always
because of someone
other than me
and by the one
destined person
who of course
has no substitute
the roles have changed
Akane wasn't a teacher anymore
and she wasn't a sad
lonely woman
trying to define herself
to the world
through a man
and god did she look
beautiful that night
preparing to set out
on her own true adventure
after finally being
given a name
I know I should say
things like
are you serious
but instead
I say
congratulations
I'm
well
thanks again
this is far enough
I won't lie
I really did enjoy
looking at your face
monkey
do you think
I'm too terrible
I really do
but there's no blame
that's kind of you
bye
I'm not very kind at all
I don't have any right
to blame her
in the end
it turned out
that I loved you more
when you were just
a weak and broken woman
what does that mean
Akane
listen
I will always remember
no matter how much
you want me to forget
always
I was mistaken
I thought I always
wanted to change you
but that was wrong
I never wanted that
in the end
I loved the way you were
before you changed
I loved the broken you
so
so know this
no matter what
I won't forget
thank you
goodbye
Akane
you
and